

HANA WIDYATARI

+6281321861427 | hanawidyatari@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/hana-widyatari/ | https://hana-widyatari.netlify.app/

Bandung, Indonesia

A technology and design enthusiast with 1 year experience in building web applications. Loved to explore and learn about programming and design. Use Typescript and Javascript with React and Vue framework as tools to build the applications. Skill in problem solving, designing, and analyzing data.

Work Experiences

Mazecare - Hongkong, SAR

Oct 2022 - Present

Software Engineer

Mazecare is a digital healthcare platform that simplifies communication between the trifecta of patient, provider, and insurer.

- Handled developing, maintaining, and improving web application for health care company using Typescript with Vue Nuxt Js as tools.
- · Maintained and developed inventory and stock management module.
- Integrated WhatsApp API and developed two ways communication module.
- Handled connecting and fetching GraphQL to client side using Pinia as state management.
- Performed debugging and testing to reduce bugs and make applications work as expected.
- · Communicating with clients to understand their project goals, needs, and requirements and come up with efficient technical solutions.

Radya Labs - Bandung, Indonesia

Mar 2022 - May 2022

Junior Frontend Developer

Radya Digital (formerly known as Radya Labs) is a mobile software development company.

- Developed and Maintained CMS web application using Typescript language with React Next Js as tools.
- Collaborated with cross-functional team (Project Manager, UI Designer, Backend Developers, and QA) to successfully completing projects.
- · Handled connecting and fetching API to client side using Axios and Zustand as state management.
- · Made the web interactive, responsive, and functional.
- Delivered to strict deadlines and received positive feedback from project manager and clients.

Ministry of Agrarian Affairs and Spatial Planing - Jakarta,

Jun 2021 - Sep 2021

Indonesia

Revalidation and Quality Control Data

The Ministry of Agrarian and Spatial Planning, organizing government affairs in the field of agrarian / land and spatial planning to assist the President Indonesia in carrying out state governance.

- Verified the population of database in the KKP's website.
- Revalidated the digital land books database in the KKP's website based on the physic of the land books for Centre of Jakarta area.
- Added and corrected the textual mistakes from the digital land books in KKP's website. Reduced mistakes digital land book by 75% per-week.
- Weekly progress of revalidation reported by officer to the Ministry of Agrarian Affairs and Spatial Planning.

PT. Inovasi Geomatika Indonesia - Bandung, Indonesia

Feb 2019 - Aug 2019

3D Model Analyst and Development Engineering

- Reconstructed laser scanner, terrestrial, and aerial photogrammetry data into 3D point cloud.
- Compiled the laser scanner, terrestrial, and photogrammetry 3D point cloud.
- Built the compiled 3D point cloud into 3D model object and justified the detail of 3D model object.
- Created virtual reality (VR) from 3D model and attached textual information such as history, location, and structures of the object.

PT. Inovasi Geomatika Indonesia - Bandung, Indonesia

Jul 2018 - Aug 2018

Internship MEP and 3D Modeler

- Built an exterior 3D modelling building with acquisition data from aerial photogrammetry using Photo-modeler.
- Built an interior 3D modelling and MEP (Mechanical Electrical and Plumbing) system from architecture building plan using ArchiCAD.
- Reported and presented the progress and final result to supervisor BIM division.

Education Level

Binar Academy Bootcamp Full-stack Web Developer @ - Jakarta, Indonesia

Jan 2022 - Aug 2022

Certificate in Full Stack Developer, 4.80/5.00

- Built an individual and team website application projects.
- Learned to code using Javascript programming language.
- Learned to design web using basic HTML, CSS integrated with DOM (Document Object Model), React with Next JS, and bootstrap

framework as frontend side.

- Learned to code with REST API and backend side using MERN (MongoDB, Express, ReactJS, Node) stack.
- Learned version control system and state management such as redux.
- Learned about testing using Jest, eslint, and CI/CD using GitHub Action.

Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember - Surabaya, Indonesia

Bachelor Degree in Geomatics Engineering, 3.58/4.00

- Geo-Innovation Bootcamp BIG 2017 National
- PKM KC national 2017 funded by DIKTI National
- Forum Commtech Integrated Initiative 2017 International

Organisational Experience

Himage Aug 2016 - Aug 2019

Member

Department organization for Geomatics Engineering Institute Technology of Sepuluh Nopember.

- · Active and support all the activity for geomatics engineering department events.
- Help organization for giving suggestion and aspiration to improve the organization.

IMGI (Ikatan Mahasiswa Geodesi Indonesia)

Aug 2015 - Aug 2019

Member

A national-scale student organization oriented towards the science and profession of Geodesy and/or Geomatics Engineering.

· Active and support all activity and event for the organization.

Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Fullstack Web Developer Bootcamp: BINAR Academy ⊚ (2022):

- Achievements: BIG 2017 Geo-Innovation Bootcamp The Best 25 ⊚ (2017):

Aug 2015 - Aug 2019